# Sam Liman

## Full-Stack Software Engineer

Denver, Colorado

303-995-9554

www.linkedin.com/in/samliman www.github.com/samliman

samlimandev@amail.com

www.samliman.com

Grounded through four years as an 'IT guy', I am a fiercely creative software developer with a passion for environmentalism and social justice. I am inspired to save the world through efficiency and precision. With 20 years of experience in customer service, I am passionate about creating solutions to help my stakeholders realize their highest potential.

#### Skills

Python; JavaScript (ES6); React; Git; MongoDB; ExpressJS; NodeJS; PostgreSQL; Jquery; SQLite; Postman; CSS; Sass; Materialize; Bootstrap; Agile; Wireframing; Authentication; Object-oriented Programming; User Stories; Bash; Windows Powershell; Command Prompt; Network Administration and Security; Software Repair, Maintenance, and Upgrades; IT Tech. Support.

### Software Development Projects

Spotless - Authenticated React/Flask playlist sharing app, using Python, Javascript, PostgreSQL, Postman, and SCSS/Materialize, with Wireframes and User Stories. spotles.herokuapp.com/ Carpe Diem Weather - Authenticated React/Flask database app, using a basic weather API, CSS, Bootstrap, Postman, Wireframing, and User Stories. carpe-diem-weather-react.herokuapp.com/ Beatless - Music database application with CRUD capabilities, created with Authentication, using CSS/Bootstrap, JavaScript, Express, MongoDB, and Postman. beatlesss.herokuapp.com/

### Education

General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive - 24-week, 800+ hour, full-stack program conducted in a classroom setting, covering both front- and back-end programming languages, libraries, tools and methodologies. Completed: February 2020 Metropolitan State University of Denver - BS (Psychology) - 2013 (3.53 GPA)

- Teacher's Assistant for Psychopharmacology in final semester.

#### Work Experience

Managed IT Services, World Wide Technology

3/2018-4/2019:

- Administration of Cisco Meraki Cloud Managed Networking Equipment at global scale.

IT Consulltant, Twin Enviro Services

11/2015-3/2018

- Implemented a wireless, VPN-linked network connecting three locations across Colorado. Replaced or upgraded all workstations and printers. Deployed MS Office 365, web-based surveillance systems, and video-conference system.

IT Assistant, ACZ Laboratories

11/2015-5/2017

- Assistant to the Systems Administrator for an enterprise with 100+ workstations, including many legacy systems controlling testing equipment. I was the POC for the service desk, and participated in long-overdue, network-wide upgrades.